WDI Unseen America Memorabilia 6313 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
WDI Unseen America Memorabilia
2007-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Workforce Development Institute
6313 MB
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Memorabilia, broadsides.
Pamphlets, postcards/trading cards, broadsides, programs, pins, business cards, publicity packs relating to the Workforce Development Institute.
7186907
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, September 25, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Working class; Workforce Development Institute
7186907
- Unseen America, New York State Publications, 2008-2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  folder 1 of 2
  - Item 1: unseenamerica NY State: What Workers See, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Francessca Accetturi; Larry Demarco; Sheri Demarco; Tinatin Javakhishvili; Gudfinna Leifsson; Bea Reiser; Eliana Rincon; Erika Rincon; Jim Zaino
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: unseenamerica New York State: Newburgh, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Joyce Quinn; Regina Brown; Toni Elmore; Toie Calhoun; Lillian Paz; Thomas Kuruvilla; Lorraine Baker
  - Item 3: What We See: Veterans in Central New York, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Sam Haddad; William Hoffman; Adam McNamara; Suzette Moore; Rick Woodward
  - Item 4: unseenamerica New York State: Working Hands, Working Lives, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Patricia Clowers; Jean Gregor; Roger Gregor; Kenneth Smith; Burt Whiteman; Diana Whiteman; Judith Whiteman
  - Item 5: unseenamerica New York State: Working Lives, Working Hands, 2008; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Miguel Angel Alvarado; Marlene Bloomer; Steven Wayne Carson; Barbara Ethan; Irene Quinlan; Catherine Randel; Bonnie Roll; Sue Rosenberg; John Steele Jr.; Veronica Strout; Cheryl Symister-Masterson; Graciela Torres Valez; Jean Van Ness; Darlene Wasser; Rut
  - Item 6: unseenamerica New York State: Pictures of Working Life Taken By Working Hands, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Damon Boston; Carol Cook; Heather Culverwell; Anna Horton; Joao Henrique Jabur Bittar; Don Jackson; Teresa Kloch; Cheryl McInerney; Jennifer Smith; Elizabeth Soha; Nancy Switzer; Jim Switzer; Jennifer Tabb; Cassandra Weeden
- Unseen America New York State Publications, 2007-2010 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  folder 2 of 2
  - Item 1: unseenamerica nys: Photos and Stories by Workers and Family of UAW Local 465, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Tammy Arquiett-Burns; Georgia Bell; Jeff Burns; Cindy Lavean; Lydia Marlar; Ray Thibault
  - Item 2: WDI 2009/10 Annual Report, 2010; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: WDI (Workforce Development Institute)
  - Item 3: unseenamerica NYS: Pictures of Working Lives Taken By Working Hands, 2007; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Robert Ban; Regina Brown; Rhonda Carter-Hoefen; Chocho Behbt; Toie Calhoun; Broger Chenez; Thomas Brooks; Dave Capone; Sidi Chivala; Miriam Chet; Daniel Cribb; Mary Lou Dwyer; Daisy Chung; Julie Dade-Howard; Liz Espinoza; Gail Cook; Deirdre Delaney; Helen
  - Item 4: Refugee Voices, 2009; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Khin Myat Naing; Soe Moe Aung; Salih Ahmed; Zaw Min; Ra Ju Kharaka; Win Yu Nwe; Zaw Myint; Arun Giri; Thura Aung; Hnin Hnin Zaw; Zaw nay Myo
- Unseenamerica New York State, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Post cards of different sizes
- Unseenamerica Pins, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  2 pins
- WDI - Workforce Development Institute Art of Labor - Art of Labor folder, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)